{
    "subject": "resource/Team_Bondi",
    "predicate": "property/location",
    "object": "resource/Sydney",
    "human_readable": "Team Bondi is located in Sydney.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9824931621551514,
            "question": "Is Team Bondi based in Sydney?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9134325981140137,
            "question": "Where is Team Bondi located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.862162172794342,
            "question": "In which country is Team Bondi situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7750949859619141,
            "question": "Team Bondi's location is in which major city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7391160130500793,
            "question": "Team Bondi's studio is based in which Australian metropolis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.644656777381897,
            "question": "What Australian city houses Team Bondi's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5811731219291687,
            "question": "What city is home to Team Bondi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5713765621185303,
            "question": "What is the geographical position of Team Bondi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43092280626296997,
            "question": "Where would you find the offices of Team Bondi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41822507977485657,
            "question": "If you wanted to visit Team Bondi, where would you go?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Team Bondi is located in Sydney.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7319_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where would you find the offices of Team Bondi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7319_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the geographical position of Team Bondi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7319_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is home to Team Bondi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7319_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7319_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7319_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7319_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7319_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7319_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7319_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7319_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7319_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7319_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7319_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents provide information that supports the fact that Team Bondi was an Australian game studio based in Sydney, as mentioned in the file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7319/re-ranker-msmarco/47.txt. This establishes a connection between Team Bondi and the city of Sydney."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is derived from the context that multiple documents mention Team Bondi being based in Sydney, Australia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}